mrfreeads.com 2013-04-13

# 

Mfreeads has created this Privacy Policy in order to help our users better understand what information we collect about them and what may happen to that information.

Overview

As part of the normal operation of our services we collect and, in some cases, may disclose information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to Mrfreeads Terms and Conditions.

Children

Children are not eligible to use our services, and we ask that minors (under the age of 13) do not post to the service or submit any personal information to us.

Information We Collect

Mrfreeads primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customised experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs and to customise our service to make your experience easier. Your forum profile is available for other users to view. This viewable profile does not include any identifying information about you, except the user name you choose upon registering, date that you joined and any other data that you chose to add to the said profile.

Please note that your personally identifiable information will be stored and processed on our servers in the U.S.A Mrfreeads will hold and transmit your information in a safe, confidential and secure environment.

We automatically track certain information based upon your traversal of our sites using cookies and other devices. We use this information for internal research on our users interests, and behaviours to better understand and serve you the user. This information may include, the URL that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your IP address.

We use data collection devices such as 'cookies' on our Web site. 'Cookies' are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customised services. The Cookies are Session Cookies, meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies but by doing so you will not be able to use this site.

Our Use of Your Information 

We use information in the files we maintain about you, and the other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Web site to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems; in particular we may examine your information to identify users with multiple accounts. You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyse site usage, improve our content and services and customise our Site's content and layout. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to meet your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use on the Web site. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information.

Our Disclosure of Your Information 

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Web site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications would always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

Financial Information.

Under some circumstances we may require some additional information, such as, but not limited, to credit card details. We use this financial information, including your name, address, and other information, as well as to bill you for use of our services. We use your financial information to bill you for services and/or products. By making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity or transaction that uses financial information on the Web sites, you consent to our providing of your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine are necessary to support and process your activities and transactions, as well as to your credit card issuer for their purposes. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process and support the transaction or activity. By purchasing, registering or making reservations for products or services of third parties offered on the Web site, or by participating in programs offered on the Web site that are administered by third parties and that require you to submit financial information in order to use them, you also consent to our providing your financial information to those third parties. Any of these various third parties may be authorised to use your financial information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. Additionally, you agree that we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such third parties in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information that you submit to us.

Advertisers.

We aggregate (gather up data across all our users accounts) personally identifiable information and may disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number and bank account number, are never disclosed to marketing advertisers.

External Service Providers.

There may be a number of services offered by external service providers that help you use our Web site. If you choose to use these optional services, and in the course of doing so, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their private policy.

Legal Requests.

mrfreeads co-operates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorise us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.

Your Use of other Users Information 

Our services also include access to private messaging in the forums. As a user of this service, you have access to other users user names and profile information. You may also gain access to other contact information of the User(s) through the regular use of private messaging and forums. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you agree that, with respect to other users personally identifiable information that you obtain through private messaging communication, the forums and email. Mrfreeads grants to you a license to use such information only for:

(a) Mrfreeads related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages.

(b) Any other purpose that such user expressly agrees to after adequate disclosure of  the purpose(s).

In all cases, you must give the user an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this Section, can you disclose personally identifiable information about another user to any third party without our consent and the consent of such other user. Mrfreeads and our users do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add a Mrfreeads user to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express written consent. To report spam from other Mrfreeads users, please use the support section to contact us.

Your Profile

Following registration, you can review and change the password you submitted during registration using the 'My Account' section.  

We may retain in our files information you have requested to be removed for certain circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored 'back up' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information would be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

Control of Your Password 

You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your password or login information to any third parties. If you choose to share this information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password or contact us immediately.

Other Information Collectors

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our Web site or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since Mrfreeads does not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

Security

Mrfreeads uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including firewall's. Mrfreeads treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, 'perfect security' does not exist on the Internet.

Notice

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. All changes to this policy are effective after posting on the Web site.
